{"data":{"createNewExamAttempt":{"attempt":{"id":"aea1048b-8143-4df1-b6e1-408a048d5c90"},"exam":{"id":"7946a823-ef60-4896-9562-434bf1e4a208","title":"AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner Exam","duration":5400,"totalQuestions":65,"questions":[{"id":"57f5e909-774f-43b9-9718-c0b61fc8225c","domain":"security","question":"You are currently running an application in a production environment, but you want to ensure that it is free of vulnerabilities. Which of the following AWS services would you need to use?","explanation":"You will need to turn to Amazon Inspector for security assessment. Not only does it identify vulnerabilities in your application, it will also spot deviations from security best practices. AWS Shield and WAF protect the application from attacks that exploit vulnerabilities, rather than identify them. And Trusted Advisor only provides recommendations on how to improve security.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/inspector/latest/userguide/inspector_introduction.html","title":"What is Amazon Inspector?"}],"answers":[{"id":"769f2c629067645d4b60e13009500c9f","text":"AWS Web Application Firewall (WAF)","correct":false},{"id":"41a831f771ef9bece59ed5160e335ae7","text":"AWS Trusted Inspector","correct":false},{"id":"637d82e8a7206e87344161109cf7112d","text":"AWS Shield","correct":false},{"id":"543096643aa6d28d9fac278e9257783d","text":"Amazon Inspector","correct":true}]},{"id":"ee56fwac-hgmj-xrxe-1u42-pucfbmasuhh1","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following is not a compute service?","explanation":"Elastic Block Store is a storage service - all others are compute services.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/products/compute/","title":"AWS Compute"}],"answers":[{"id":"3d6cbd7db2a4fa389808ea6f4a5fc1bc","text":"Elastic Beanstalk","correct":false},{"id":"34bc95906489c2d5c9583e3230cd48b2","text":"Elastic Block Store","correct":true},{"id":"81b22456f78954c460ce2f531b5e048f","text":"EC2","correct":false},{"id":"04a7da3c5b04cad85da1eebb92315b8b","text":"Lambda","correct":false}]},{"id":"69916ab3-c78a-4abd-86a8-5dc73e90916a","domain":"tech","question":"Your manager approaches you this morning to tell you there has been a surprise audit announced by the internal audit team for all of your company's AWS Accounts. Which service would you use to provide the necessary information to the audit team?","explanation":"AWS CloudTrail is a service that enables governance, compliance, operational and risk auditing of your AWS account.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/cloudtrail/","title":"AWS CloudTrail"}],"answers":[{"id":"1aa2d5ab75afef6fa4ccd1e3b22174d4","text":"QuickSight","correct":false},{"id":"9deb03cd21d41a691cdc24bfaab2820c","text":"Inspector","correct":false},{"id":"311bdda432aba736b8dcb987523c0c92","text":"CloudWatch","correct":false},{"id":"92fbbd5478621cf8f70624389759b44c","text":"CloudTrail","correct":true}]},{"id":"o8aqfsp4-kk6k-gyj7-frq7-4bpn7iv5zqm8","domain":"concepts","question":"You have a mission-critical application which must be globally available at all times. Which deployment strategy should you follow?","explanation":"A Multi-Region deployment will best ensure global availability. While it can be the most expensive, and complex to configure, Multi-Regional architectures will ensure that even if all Availability Zones in a single region fail due to a catastrophic event, your data will remain accessible.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/AWS_Cloud_Best_Practices.pdf","title":"Architecting for The Cloud: Best Practices"}],"answers":[{"id":"ec206762c0bea997a5b0f91783cce54f","text":"Multi-Availability Zone","correct":false},{"id":"86b2c5243e03e210528f020bad4efdb9","text":"Multi-VPC in two AWS Regions","correct":false},{"id":"91d7ff212b9bda483701aeb4209ae5ec","text":"Deploy to all Availability Zones in your home region.","correct":false},{"id":"e4ec2833a31f482abfdb31691f0351dc","text":"Multi-Region","correct":true}]},{"id":"8ae68d9e-7bf8-41c2-996a-a01fb1bf966a","domain":"billing","question":"Which tool can help you to compare the cost of hosting resources in AWS vs the cost of hosting in a traditional data centre?","explanation":"The TCO calculators allow you to estimate the cost savings when using AWS and provide a detailed set of reports.  Pricing Calculator can be used to estimate potential AWS spend, and AWS Budgets & Billing Alarms can help keep spend under control by alerting you when you breach a threshold.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/tco-calculator/","title":"AWS TCO Calculator"}],"answers":[{"id":"1a98a10ad310a9ed66414dd3acb48e72","text":"AWS Pricing Calculator","correct":false},{"id":"6b6f2097ec6555c2e09b7ed23571b3c5","text":"AWS Billing Alarms","correct":false},{"id":"e32a801c8e0beab6abb9361e937365be","text":"AWS Budgets","correct":false},{"id":"e84e1dd83afcda636af8a6ae32a58cef","text":"AWS TCO Calculator","correct":true}]},{"id":"bfoxiudd-ep8s-9jah-t2ho-96nct3a3mjfh","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following data archival services is extremely inexpensive, but can have a multi-hour data-retrieval window?","explanation":"Glacier offers extremely inexpensive data archival, but requires a 3-5 hour data-retrieval window for standard retrievals - though this time can be reduced for a price. Other S3 storage tiers, including Infrequent Access (S3-IA) can all be accessed immediately, but some may incur additional fees for accessing","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/glacier/","title":"About Glacier"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/s3/storage-classes/?nc=sn&loc=3","title":"S3 Storage Classes"}],"answers":[{"id":"4def2a084469f97f6372bfaf0823941b","text":"Glacier","correct":true},{"id":"e2ab7c65b21ed8cc1c3b642b5e36429e","text":"S3","correct":false},{"id":"4340570ba672bfa48cd45e3f026c01d1","text":"S3 - IA","correct":false},{"id":"31e831ec49678aed7f467f791d1f8704","text":"S3 - RRS","correct":false},{"id":"e9a5105fa288ef2b71c037e42d665d91","text":"S3 - OneZone-IA","correct":false}]},{"id":"upv9n2ts-iwzj-4vez-gyls-rnpppswzz8zm","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below is true about root accounts on AWS?","explanation":"The root user has access to absolutely everything in an AWS account, and therefore should not be used for normal day to day activities and be reserved for when things go wrong. AWS will never ask you for any usernames or passwords as part of a support request  - so any request to do so should be treated with suspicion. The root user cannot be disabled.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/id_root-user.html","title":"The AWS Root User"}],"answers":[{"id":"3db3937d9b6115b761fee0d0a7ad9975","text":"The root user is the recommended way to work in the AWS Console","correct":false},{"id":"8d2e8228cfcd751c2f8d90fe0712a9f0","text":"The root user will be used by AWS should they need to help you with something in your account","correct":false},{"id":"547527745e6b2e9620cf7400b9c03c91","text":"The root user has full access to everything in the AWS account","correct":true},{"id":"5c25f0724b86a34c79909772ae00ddd2","text":"The root user should be disabled after you create an Admin user","correct":false},{"id":"eb189b7195d97fe576a8babd440bd471","text":"The root user should not be used for day to day activities","correct":true}]},{"id":"9da21f94-7d9e-4bcf-8c7c-fc97b0634977","domain":"security","question":"Your company has updated its security policies to include cloud workloads as well as those running on-premises. Your manager would like a report of which technologies will require configuration changes. Which of the following will not be included in the report because they are the responsibility of AWS?","explanation":"In the AWS Shared Responsibility Model, AWS in responsible for managing host operating systems. Users are responsible for managing guest operating systems, as well as Security Group Firewalls, Amazon Aurora data encryption, and S3 access control lists.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"64f8358ae4360eddd993acde2d19789c","text":"Amazon Aurora data encryption","correct":false},{"id":"63c21f07ff59add0f7e474ef5ec57c2e","text":"Security Group firewalls","correct":false},{"id":"8061595e3a5f2fb2195dd627dd35f5d2","text":"Host operating systems","correct":true},{"id":"331bd4e2a8ab147e5a6a47e5b9c40d65","text":"S3 Access Control Lists","correct":false}]},{"id":"aosxkeh9-qevj-zztz-qgkg-lo0glwr2ccoh","domain":"billing","question":"By default, when using consolidated billing, which of the below will the master paying account be able to do in the member account?","explanation":"By default, using Consolidated Billing only allows the master account to view the billing information from the member accounts - no access is automatically granted for users in the master account into the member accounts beyond this. ","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/consolidated-billing.html","title":"AWS Consolidated Billing"}],"answers":[{"id":"3dbb078ea9c1eaf843d213ba217af3e8","text":"View billing information","correct":true},{"id":"25e6de5387e3157c014e2c6f2b0e810e","text":"Make changes to resources","correct":false},{"id":"29f838d6149e7ff36b4692f879dbd0a3","text":"Grant access to member account to other users","correct":false},{"id":"54e29f93505b20fe2cc8af1cce96a33b","text":"View any data stored","correct":false}]},{"id":"bd8ac490-21fe-451e-a3e6-6dfa221fb389","domain":"concepts","question":"Deploying your EC2 instances across multiple AZs will help address which Cloud Concept?","explanation":"Having resources across multiple AZ is one way to design for High Availability - the concept that your services in cloud should be designed to tolerate failures in the underlying cloud infrastructure. AWS allows you to do this by providing Availability Zones - each one is independent from the others, and a failure in one should not impact the others. Therefore, if you deploy your application in 2 instances in 2 AZs, and one of the AZs fails, you will still have 1 instance running your application. Automation relates simplifying common repeated tasks and removing the human element. Although scaleability and elasticity (the ability to increase resources according to needs and the ability to go up and down in resources as needed) look like they might fit, as we are talking specifically about Multiple AZs in the question High Availability is the more correct answer","links":[],"answers":[{"id":"2a76e3da23b5e753e4ce6c1aa1fc827c","text":"Elasticity","correct":false},{"id":"caea8340e2d186a540518d08602aa065","text":"Automation","correct":false},{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":false},{"id":"520b661a272c9e6f55f469cc9c24193d","text":"High Availability","correct":true}]},{"id":"86d0ccb9-ab67-4952-a7ea-0fea12fc6c1f","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below are TRUE statements when it comes to data security in AWS?","explanation":"Under the Shared Responsibility Model, AWS takes responsibility for managing all the hardware (including access, patching and other maintenance) and software required to deliver the service - which includes security. The customer is responsible for who can access the data itself.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"0ed894aaf38bd44ba33d1612854617d0","text":"AWS is responsible for managing who can access the data","correct":false},{"id":"6e8271456f0c471167caae0d75aab487","text":"The customer is responsible for the security of the hardware the data resides on","correct":false},{"id":"2844802845f801aded529f1d22c63d82","text":"AWS is responsible for the security of the software that manages the data","correct":true},{"id":"599dca975551e5a41106ce454a46e4e0","text":"AWS is responsible for the security of the hardware the data resides on","correct":true},{"id":"7a0bc438686e10d5e1ab102d0dc0e4a9","text":"The customer is responsible for the security of the software that manages the data","correct":false},{"id":"9f02eb6c8050b89db31831403951787b","text":"The customer is responsible for managing who can access the data","correct":true}]},{"id":"aaa7dqnz-f7nv-g9bl-zfw2-2xko23ptcj2t","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below are you responsible for managing when storing data in S3?","explanation":"Under the Shared Responsibility Model for managed services, AWS takes responsibility for managing all the hardware (including access, patching and other maintenance). When it comes to S3, the customer is responsible for all aspects of the data being stored on S3, and who has access to manage the S3 service for that account","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"3278fa01d394d47605876669eaea2957","text":"Who has access to the network hardware","correct":false},{"id":"6c507c7b28d852214aa62ba95c5c7009","text":"Who has access to data you stored on the S3 Service","correct":true},{"id":"f661780dbe84a95f44f8622698e4b2a9","text":"Who has access to the S3 Infrastructure Software","correct":false},{"id":"2f6823eab5248af1500c3b8329fab352","text":"Who has access to the S3 Service","correct":true},{"id":"ae48532652716e286fa0be350d5545e3","text":"Who has access to the storage hardware","correct":false}]},{"id":"8x0x6jdm-e0n1-0rb6-ibad-we2hbkuaxgvw","domain":"tech","question":"You need to store a collection of objects that can also be accessed from a different AWS Region. Which service should you use to do this?","explanation":"S3 allows you to access objects from anywhere in the world - as long as the appropriate permissions are set!","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/dev/Welcome.html","title":"About S3"}],"answers":[{"id":"6ebb7423072c5943f52c11274fd71b0b","text":"DynamoDB","correct":false},{"id":"e66f7962b812129e4a3890b1dab122c0","text":"Elastic Container Service","correct":false},{"id":"e2ab7c65b21ed8cc1c3b642b5e36429e","text":"S3","correct":true},{"id":"248c1b0bcb74394beb4a08030c4a6847","text":"EBS","correct":false}]},{"id":"c3f7fb72-1aba-4b4a-a88d-ab28709130ae","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following services are available 24x7 for all AWS Support Plans?","explanation":"All AWS Support plans provide 24x7 access to customer service, documentation, and support forums. For 24x7 access to Cloud Support Engineers, you will specifically need to get a Business or Enterprise Support plan.","links":[{"url":"https://console.aws.amazon.com/support/plans/home?#/","title":"AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"ba4ffb983499bcebaa93c87030f33728","text":"Cloud Support Engineers","correct":false},{"id":"a42a69de8cb0bc12c105962bb2df8561","text":"Support forums","correct":true},{"id":"2273d1167a6212812d95dc8fadbae78e","text":"Customer service","correct":true},{"id":"df710f89ebb9e663bd3d66607a0bf413","text":"AWS documentation","correct":true}]},{"id":"3edc2ffd-d684-4cf1-83f9-b782b6782711","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following pricing models are available for EC2?","explanation":"EC2 has four different pricing models, On Demand, Reserved, Spot and Dedicated Hosts. Each pricing model has been created for different workload types and use cases.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/","title":"Amazon EC2 pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"244492cdce9dce0555c52ebe1182e0a3","text":"On Demand","correct":true},{"id":"acbe4e201e8e2ac67830983f9c8d7970","text":"Dedicated Hosts","correct":true},{"id":"942d4e37dd5607ab68e54755540d4a47","text":"Reserved","correct":true},{"id":"a687560297f056cb18ffb527b46f79b4","text":"Dot Instances","correct":false},{"id":"abf84cb49aaf1ec8157f80e4d27d011e","text":"Hybrid Instances","correct":false}]},{"id":"1638290e-2fb4-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following does AWS use to notify you by email when you exceed 85% of your Free Tier limits for each service?","explanation":"AWS uses Budgets to notify you when you exceed 85% of your Free Tier limits for each service you’re using by sending you an email. Picking Cost Explorer as the answer is misleading; it is actually a visualizer you can use to analyze your spend, but it does not alert you on your Free Tier usage. Organizations centralizes the management of your resources; it has nothing to do with usage alerts. And Personal Health Dashboard allows you to visualize the status, rather than usage, of your resources.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/tracking-free-tier-usage.html","title":"Tracking Your Free Tier Usage"}],"answers":[{"id":"b1820ee1cf68e2e65f263ff7bb207626","text":"AWS Organizations","correct":false},{"id":"c7f176d72688fd87853e31b84159d541","text":"AWS Cost Explorer","correct":false},{"id":"e32a801c8e0beab6abb9361e937365be","text":"AWS Budgets","correct":true},{"id":"d189bb1b260dc3da48b6e6f5e1ec6879","text":"AWS Personal Health Dashboard","correct":false}]},{"id":"150e71c2-9b46-4a48-bed4-ef89f73570ae","domain":"tech","question":"Although you know that your Amazon Elastic Block Store (EBS) volumes are designed to be highly reliable, you want to further mitigate the possibility of a failure. Which of the following should you do?","explanation":"Backup of the EBS volumes can be created by taking point-in-time snapshots. These components are stored in S3. ","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/EBSSnapshots.html","title":"Amazon EBS Snapshots"},{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/aws-building-fault-tolerant-applications.pdf?did=wp_card&trk=wp_card","title":"Fault-Tolerant Components on AWS"}],"answers":[{"id":"e2f843acc6781a153857118f92da89f4","text":"Mitigating the possibility of a failure is not necessary.","correct":false},{"id":"a2a7a68497095df080fb01033b2aea46","text":"Create backups of the EBS volumes in Amazon RDS.","correct":false},{"id":"2f63e74501f200b9859c7b5976101e79","text":"Make copies of the EBS volumes and store them in Amazon S3.","correct":false},{"id":"44023459578ef9dc57780fc55ee56f7d","text":"Take snapshots of the EBS volumes.","correct":true}]},{"id":"89c58d68-554a-45ea-9da8-fcf90103d4e8","domain":"concepts","question":"The Chief Marketing Officer of the hotel chain you work for would like to implement voice recognition capabilities in rooms so customers can request services without picking up the phone. Competitors have already begun rolling out these technologies in an attempt to improve their customers’ experience. Which benefit of the AWS cloud would you most emphasize to the CMO in your business case for creating an AWS-based solution?","explanation":"The AWS cloud provides instant access to new technologies. Companies can move with agility to satisfy new business requirements and meet competitive demands. There is a very low barrier of entry for innovation. If a solution is not meeting expectations, services can be instantly de-provisioned. The other three options will also prove to be benefits of deploying in the AWS cloud, but the use case emphasizes the need to move quickly against competitive threats.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/what-is-cloud-computing/","title":"What is Cloud Computing?"}],"answers":[{"id":"6cdf2174e24cf3e60f016e85f00c34ff","text":"Deploy Globally in Minutes","correct":false},{"id":"2a76e3da23b5e753e4ce6c1aa1fc827c","text":"Elasticity","correct":false},{"id":"ecbe6eb71bcb646d89d2e361dfa84c21","text":"Cost Savings","correct":false},{"id":"241bb470b0110efc8b5609f7311b0bb1","text":"Agility","correct":true}]},{"id":"xun4oj55-ptum-ekl7-y5ot-pqhc5t5psvxi","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following support plans features unlimited (customer-side) contacts and unlimited support cases?","explanation":"Both Enterprise and Business support plans feature unlimited (customer-side) contacts and unlimited support cases.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/compare-plans/","title":"Compare AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false},{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":true},{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false},{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":true}]},{"id":"77471ce7-4336-4912-9c33-ecfc5d174a41","domain":"billing","question":"You want to monitor your costs of using your AWS services and receive alerts when the thresholds you defined are met. Which of the following AWS Budget types should you create?","explanation":"You need to create a cost budget with AWS Budgets if you want to monitor the cost of using your AWS services.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/budgets-managing-costs.html","title":"Managing Your Costs with Budgets"}],"answers":[{"id":"bd4ad96569591af6420d456b8176c90d","text":"Savings Plans Budget","correct":false},{"id":"825a98fa534bb772e00d7b7571f0217f","text":"Reservation Budget","correct":false},{"id":"3f3eb4d8c9ecc531c5a784bcc5e608b5","text":"Usage Budget","correct":false},{"id":"7d45335a770dd2fc66658fb908bb7f9a","text":"Cost Budget","correct":true}]},{"id":"5fd1imv7-lqes-7e9n-vz33-eau71532v2ly","domain":"security","question":"How does AWS Shield Standard help protect your environment?","explanation":"AWS Shield Standard is included at no extra cost but will only block DDOS attacks on your AWS resources - it will not scan the contents of incoming or outgoing traffic (this is a function of WAF) and will not protect your environment from viruses","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/waf/latest/developerguide/shield-chapter.html","title":"AWS Shield"}],"answers":[{"id":"3e6fc5c29a49e9d5c54bd4950ad5cbe0","text":"By scanning outgoing application traffic for sensitive information","correct":false},{"id":"84009024e233c4995b00c514474f0ae5","text":"By Blocking DDOS attacks","correct":true},{"id":"b1d6309ddb9cc2f856af5a3bab83f37e","text":"By scanning incoming application traffic for know attacks","correct":false},{"id":"55063c26653acc06bd00cc13e1acc3a4","text":"By scanning your instances for viruses","correct":false}]},{"id":"fd097342-1bc8-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"concepts","question":"CloudFront is used to route users to the edge location that provides the lowest amount of time delay in delivering content. Which of the following terms describes this 'time delay'?","explanation":"Latency refers to the amount of time delay during the processing of network data. CloudFront is AWS’s content delivery network service, which routes users to the edge location with the lowest latency. That means the content will be delivered as fast as possible.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonCloudFront/latest/DeveloperGuide/Introduction.html","title":"What is Amazon CloudFront?"}],"answers":[{"id":"e3cba4d3cce16ddf0ce129e981fb5bc2","text":"resiliency","correct":false},{"id":"314a0d25c2c847aaa07e42887fda1f7b","text":"scalability","correct":false},{"id":"7883a7305bcbd394f768e04b9e800f53","text":"latency","correct":true},{"id":"aa3d4919f7245b97e2663e9bd2c15100","text":"elasticity","correct":false}]},{"id":"1s9oou1o-9lmx-321m-4ite-iqy9x7zuv18y","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following is AWS' managed database service that is compatible with MySQL, but provides better performance?","explanation":"Aurora is AWS' managed database service that is up to 5X faster than a traditional MySQL database. PostgreSQL, DynamoDB, and MariaDB are all different database technologies which are not directly compatible with MySQL","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/rds/aurora/","title":"About Aurora"}],"answers":[{"id":"509e0895bd82e3315e79018a6ce02181","text":"Aurora","correct":true},{"id":"6ebb7423072c5943f52c11274fd71b0b","text":"DynamoDB","correct":false},{"id":"399bd1ee587245ecac6f39beaa99886f","text":"PostgreSQL","correct":false},{"id":"7f9733e208088b1ce6df3d4be1765396","text":"MariaDB","correct":false}]},{"id":"1cfba8e0-0fb8-11ea-8d71-362b9e155667","domain":"billing","question":"You have EC2 and RDS instances, Redshift and Elasticsearch clusters, and an SNS topic in your AWS environment. Which of these services support reserved pricing?","explanation":"Amazon SNS is the only one of the five mentioned services that does not have reserved pricing. On the other hand, Amazon EC2, RDS, Redshift, and Elasticsearch do.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/","title":"Amazon EC2 Pricing"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/rds/pricing/","title":"Amazon RDS Pricing"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/redshift/pricing/","title":"Amazon Redshift Pricing"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/elasticsearch-service/pricing/","title":"Amazon Elasticsearch Service Pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"0221d4f5950f35dfcf98f6a60f60d20d","text":" Elasticsearch and SNS","correct":false},{"id":"fcb02ff285a97f0ed386c6cfe36b02f4","text":"EC2, RDS, Redshift, and Elasticsearch","correct":true},{"id":"3ec389f2e16e0e0443f3ef49d2b58d05","text":"EC2 and RDS","correct":false},{"id":"9d6fbf729ccc02278cc50176a91ed3fe","text":"EC2, Redshift, and SNS","correct":false},{"id":"65e4dd05e0a1392e55661f27717e96cb","text":"RDS, Redshift, Elasticsearch, and SNS","correct":false}]},{"id":"8af9065f-42ab-4684-937d-6ff9a21fce3a","domain":"tech","question":"You visit a clients site and get called into a corridor discussion. You are asked to describe the new (2019) URL structure for objects in S3.  Which of these do you use as a description.","explanation":"AWS has updated the URL format for objects in S3 in order to partition the name space.  This will introduce more consistency, but be aware that there are still multiple variation depending on feature and location.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/blogs/aws/amazon-s3-path-deprecation-plan-the-rest-of-the-story/","title":"New S3 path format"},{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/general/latest/gr/rande.html#s3_region","title":"S3 Regional Endpoints"}],"answers":[{"id":"a91ee87d632a84e3d44d1f44d80dc38e","text":" https, then the AWS S3 regional endpoint, then slash, then the bucket name, then slash, then the object name","correct":false},{"id":"9b571c57c4bcb1635a0422505e741908","text":" https, then the bucket name, then dot, then the AWS S3 regional endpoint, then slash, then the object name","correct":true},{"id":"e9fd54ece61badbfe41eb84932fcb635","text":" http, then the object name, then dot, then the AWS S3 regional endpoint, then dot, then bucket the name","correct":false},{"id":"db8e7027e46c062db1befedc330f0884","text":" https, then the AWS S3 regional endpoint, then dot, then the bucket name, then slash, then the object name","correct":false},{"id":"ab8096a72368e95dc6011f1758564494","text":" https, then the object name, then slash, then the AWS S3 regional endpoint, then slash, then bucket the name","correct":false},{"id":"f2a5230ac12d8264aebebe8dfedd74a5","text":" http, then the bucket name, then dot, then the AWS S3 regional endpoint, then slash, then the object name","correct":false},{"id":"ae3cbeae173c8a519b7847f15141def6","text":" https, then the bucket name, then slash, then the AWS S3 regional endpoint, then slash, then the object name","correct":false}]},{"id":"27ohq41k-k7qp-a4r2-2r7m-05za454l4hk3","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following AWS Support levels offers 24x7 support via phone or chat?","explanation":"The Business and Enterprise support plans, the two most expensive plans, offer 24 X 7 support via phone or chat. Neither of the other support plans (Basic and Developer) offer Phone support. Individual is also not a real support plan","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/compare-plans/","title":"Compare AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false},{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":true},{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false},{"id":"2dd4472245a696bc0b4b944db2a8b519","text":"Individual","correct":false}]},{"id":"1a184992-2fe5-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following are advantages of using Amazon Machine Images (AMIs) backed by Amazon Elastic Block Storage (EBS), rather than by Elastic Compute Cloud (EC2) instance storage?","explanation":"When launching an EC2 instance, Amazon EBS speeds up the process over the EC2 instance storage. In addition, EBS uses persistent storage, which means that the data will be retained despite instance stops, terminations, or hardware failures. EC2 instance storage is ephemeral, which means data is lost when an instance is stopped, terminated of fails.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/RootDeviceStorage.html","title":"Amazon EC2 Root Device Volume"}],"answers":[{"id":"6650a3b982bb9d582cf6cbdfa6218802","text":"Unlike EC2 instance store, EBS uses persistent storage.","correct":true},{"id":"6bc959028a0d1f69905507976853f2a2","text":"EBS launches faster than EC2 instance storage.","correct":true},{"id":"0102366a40ae9c7c88ef2d94a1b441ed","text":"EBS offers more storage space.","correct":false},{"id":"cb69533987635ed7b48a30fb480be74c","text":"EBS is memory-optimized.","correct":false}]},{"id":"f9bc3071-e017-426b-bb59-bebf2bb60194","domain":"billing","question":"You need an AWS support plan for your production workloads, but want to keep costs to a minimum. Which of the following plans should you choose?","explanation":"The Business Support plan is specifically designed for production workloads in AWS. On one end, Basic Support is included for all AWS customers, and Developer Support plan is best suited for experimenting or testing in AWS. On the other end, there’s the Enterprise Support plan, which is ideal for business and mission-critical workloads.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/plans/","title":"Compare AWS Support Plans"}],"answers":[{"id":"d6e6cb19e3b9c02f89d6cd54cfa7c613","text":"Business","correct":true},{"id":"672caf27f5363dc833bda5099775e891","text":"Developer","correct":false},{"id":"972e73b7a882d0802a4e3a16946a2f94","text":"Basic","correct":false},{"id":"a0f27638260642afb474516cc918407e","text":"Enterprise","correct":false}]},{"id":"30rp7hn8-3uti-zql0-ays0-x3qfjnnnaax9","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are geographic areas that host two or more Availability Zones?","explanation":"A Region is a geographic area that hosts two or more Availability Zones.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/about-aws/global-infrastructure/","title":"AWS Global Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"2bdbf4724b81ff0529e32fdb1af28130","text":"AWS Origins","correct":false},{"id":"0ed2343b7ec3f778399e20cf93f8f507","text":"Compute Zones","correct":false},{"id":"17d8fc1e4ceb765476776889d7f6c5ab","text":"Edge Locations","correct":false},{"id":"5948f3347ebc02ebc690227c059661e1","text":"Regions","correct":true}]},{"id":"8dmul9q1-wi30-bo4k-81j9-ztcv7dgeoybt","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following EC2 instance types will realize a savings over time in exchange for a contracted term-of-service?","explanation":"EC2 Reserved Instances offer significant discounts for a contracted term-of-service, of up to 75% off. On-Demand instances are charged equally per-hour, regardless of how long they're run for. Spot instances are cheaper than On-Demand instances, but aren't intended for long term use","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/","title":"Amazon EC2 Pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"991236e27b7cb98a2eeff8897b3e0bb4","text":"Spot instances","correct":false},{"id":"2a80e91907ea76d424690185914b6eae","text":"On-demand instances","correct":false},{"id":"bcc129e8d9496a05a331c903d4c5bcb0","text":"Reserved instances","correct":true},{"id":"409aa157dda2d7faab6bf2938e322891","text":"Discount instances","correct":false}]},{"id":"ou2xrht1-cmrp-ebhu-q7hc-6u9cs5io40sa","domain":"tech","question":"You have been asked to archive some data into Glacier that needs to be encrypted. What is the easiest way to achieve this?","explanation":"Data stored in Glacier is encrypted by default so nothing else needs to be done. Although you can encrypt your data before sending it to Glacier, unless you need the extra security this brings over using the inbuilt encryption this is not needed. Encrypting the data in-place once it is in Glacier is not possible so is not a valid option.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/glacier/faqs/#security","title":"Glacier Security"}],"answers":[{"id":"75e47247890c290fc902a7b79b4b463a","text":"Glacier is not compatible with encrypted data, so it is the wrong choice for this - use S3 instead","correct":false},{"id":"b696238705f80058d9d00879db588871","text":"Once the data is in Glacier use the AWS Console to encrypt it.","correct":false},{"id":"65e9dbba16de862ca7d6300307bbbfe7","text":"Encrypt the data locally on your server before sending it to Glacier","correct":false},{"id":"9f250e24aef2a0c99a9464ccb839ca74","text":"Send the data to Glacier and do nothing more - all data in Glacier is encrypted by default","correct":true}]},{"id":"561b98dd-beb4-4111-8cb8-b5609a124873","domain":"tech","question":"What benefits can CloudFront bring to your e-commerce website?","explanation":"CloudFront provides the ability to cache both static and dynamic content in 200 points of presence located around the world, ensuring quick response times can be had by customers when retrieving cached website content. This inclueds protections with AWS WAF and AWS Shield. No additional analytics will necessarily be available, nor is CloudFront a database solution","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/cloudfront/features/","title":"Amazon CloudFront Infrastructure"}],"answers":[{"id":"286fe6e5d97e4ad18aac77cef2b5e28c","text":"Increased application availability","correct":true},{"id":"3559eb841146fbbde9ede18594e319f1","text":"Protection against network and application layer attacks via WAF","correct":true},{"id":"61c592ef1e234bfa1834570f2238d22f","text":"Advanced analytics into customer journeys","correct":false},{"id":"bb42b85b5fcfff06d034f3102a1daa9e","text":"Lower latency for customers of your e-commerce website","correct":true},{"id":"6c47d5971e79af6daf2b24070bd1e8ac","text":"Scalable managed database which integrates seamlessly with Lambda and EC2","correct":false}]},{"id":"uvop23ho-2fn6-04p8-5luy-ybljxy0o0477","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following services helps you to deliver your content to your customers faster?","explanation":"Amazon CloudFront is a content delivery network that speeds the delivery of content to your users.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/cloudfront/","title":"About CloudFront"}],"answers":[{"id":"bef6cb89241de238f082cb243307ad1b","text":"CloudFront","correct":true},{"id":"02f85544eeded6ef1b6c40d62bcadddd","text":"Amazon Elastic File System","correct":false},{"id":"e2ab7c65b21ed8cc1c3b642b5e36429e","text":"S3","correct":false},{"id":"34bc95906489c2d5c9583e3230cd48b2","text":"Elastic Block Store","correct":false}]},{"id":"5d7bea17-63ec-412b-bb14-bd0a1f5c4683","domain":"concepts","question":"If you have a new application and you are not sure about future demand, which of the below characteristics of cloud make cloud an ideal place to host it?","explanation":"No upfront & Pay as you go mean that you do not need an initial outlay of capital for resources to build in cloud, and only need to pay for what you use going forward. These combined with the ability to consume more resources when needed (Scalability) mean that cloud is a great way to host applications that have dynamic requirements. No Single Points of Failure and High Availability should be included in any design, but are not intrinsic to cloud. Similarly, although Performance Efficiency is key, this comes down to you application and it's design, and is not a characteristic of the cloud. ","links":[],"answers":[{"id":"2d215ebfc0280f8163d071454ec7ce01","text":"Scalability","correct":true},{"id":"bc368b371822f4e7df28c5768582dde8","text":"Performance Efficiency","correct":false},{"id":"9043a5d84d85473bd60ab9b11f10b04b","text":"No single point of failure","correct":false},{"id":"5c751a74a73417fb82a2cc45c4edc2cb","text":"No upfront","correct":true},{"id":"520b661a272c9e6f55f469cc9c24193d","text":"High Availability","correct":false},{"id":"e95a95951d99b5f038c688bf69bd5a01","text":"Pay as you go","correct":true}]},{"id":"1ad299fd-63d9-4a60-9949-d88b086002cf","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below are TRUE when running a database in an EC2 Instance?","explanation":"In this case - as the database is being run in an EC2 instance, all aspects of database updates and access is the responsibility of the customer. Similarly as it is and EC2 instance, the customer is responsible for OS patching. Under the Shared Responsibility Model, AWS takes responsibility for managing all the hardware (including access, patching and other maintenance) and software required to deliver the service - which in this case is the EC2 instance - anything to do with the instance itself is the responsibility of the customer ","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"9f9f41256e31feca524f1209e25d70fa","text":"The customer is responsible for updating the database software","correct":true},{"id":"c7098373cbee0fc9617269a6d3765dd4","text":"AWS is responsible for updating the database software","correct":false},{"id":"0d6e04dd939a298f20dd927b2a10aa7c","text":"AWS is responsible for updating the operating system","correct":false},{"id":"52f2eff0e91b46fe3007ca238393c185","text":"The customer is responsible for managing access to the database","correct":true},{"id":"42d5fd24fef6883fb899e3afd050b5a5","text":"The customer is responsible for updating the operating system","correct":true},{"id":"199f4eaff96b0da13d07770ee0ff2ab4","text":"AWS is responsible for managing access to the database","correct":false}]},{"id":"hgb6veam-i287-99i8-3v3f-0sxjtcea43qf","domain":"tech","question":"How does S3 Transfer Acceleration help you get your data into S3 quicker?","explanation":"S3 Transfer Acceleration uses AWS' network of Edge Locations to ingest data, and then uses the most optimal path within its own network to reach S3. Although compression and splitting data up before upload can also help speed things up, these are not offered by transfer acceleration. AWS does not let you send in data on your own disks, and although Snowball does let you to send data in without going across the internet, it is only useful when working with massive amounts of data.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/dev/transfer-acceleration.html","title":"Amazon S3 Transfer Acceleration"}],"answers":[{"id":"bded189801290994bc7203f5c28e9812","text":"By using AWS's network of Edge Locations to upload to a location closest to you before taking the most optimal path within AWS's network","correct":true},{"id":"9e82d26d8d807aff3537debfbdbbfa3f","text":"By splitting up your data into smaller chunks and uploading it simultaneously, then putting it back together on S3","correct":false},{"id":"25e2178eda752fbf1b65aca4d8e31d7e","text":"By letting you send the data in on a disk your provide (saving on upload times) then copying it to S3","correct":false},{"id":"7152ecba5a6dedddfb04c7c1751a7fc1","text":"By compressing your data to make it smaller for upload, then de-compressing it onto S3","correct":false}]},{"id":"1wf5g4cl-1eei-cxmu-red3-wkm59ywgq86h","domain":"tech","question":"With AWS Relational Database Service (RDS), which of the following are you responsible for?","explanation":"You are responsible only for the optimization of your application that uses RDS - AWS will take care of the rest as this is considered a Managed Service.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/rds/","title":"About RDS"}],"answers":[{"id":"bc967dc2d57e6eff184a821bf7577a80","text":"Scaling","correct":false},{"id":"6bb1aca01fa54044f3ec9ae581b4620f","text":"Operating system installation and patching","correct":false},{"id":"7b4eef372e52b848a7e0f93e59b06d70","text":"All of these","correct":false},{"id":"89f8bb80ca1403422295c6ad48f8cac7","text":"Database backups","correct":false},{"id":"5f4dc8e976d91d69670d0a272e0ee6e3","text":"Database software installation and patching","correct":false},{"id":"a514531b35c90598677ddee7c4b1afd9","text":"The optimization of your application using RDS","correct":true}]},{"id":"nfy6hmhv-trpt-lh3v-z6zh-4icv8kpv7xn6","domain":"concepts","question":"When setting up an Organization in AWS, which of the below is true when selecting which features to enable?","explanation":"With AWS Organizations, Consolidated Billing is always enabled. All other features are either enabled as a group, or disabled as a group - that is, you cannot individually enable or disable a feature - it's all or nothing!","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/en_pv/organizations/latest/userguide/orgs_getting-started_concepts.html","title":"AWS Organizations Terminology and Concepts"}],"answers":[{"id":"125540f5091c07ae2a9b7b8c0d95a432","text":"You can select to have just Consolidated Billing enabled","correct":true},{"id":"4890bb732d34952682735fd4950bcae8","text":"You can select to have Consolidated Billing, plus all other features enabled","correct":true},{"id":"ea31b0ef93ed02b05984774a32d72054","text":"You can select to have Consolidated Billing, then pick which other individual features you want enabled ","correct":false},{"id":"fd07b14b5f6a4065154c418c232ecd89","text":"You can select to have Consolidated Billing disabled, then pick which of the other features you want enabled.","correct":false}]},{"id":"zlyf2s8s-kula-sxtl-s07a-i3uh455n1hnu","domain":"security","question":"Which credentials can you use to access the AWS Management console?","explanation":"You use a username and password to log into the AWS console, although Access key and Secret Access key can be used to access some APIs programmatically","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/console/","title":"The AWS Management Console"}],"answers":[{"id":"4dd4dfb52929ef230415ada1a4169dc1","text":"Your Security Token","correct":false},{"id":"be677306ceb7d966e7a06ee1bf387acf","text":"Your Access key","correct":false},{"id":"afc76c6d8222878e0449abb2ea16838f","text":"Your Username and Password","correct":true},{"id":"2a7454c71a60c06ab2189283f1788e09","text":"Your Secret Access key","correct":false}]},{"id":"5d3e351c-1f62-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following constitute Multi-Factor Authentication for signing into the AWS Management Console?","explanation":"Multi-factor authentication, or MFA, adds an extra layer of protection to your user name and password when logging in to the AWS Management Console. To sign in, you would need two factors, which are 1.) the user name and password; and 2.) an authentication code from an AWS-supported MFA software app.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/iam/features/mfa/","title":"IAM - Multi-factor Authentication"}],"answers":[{"id":"4cf20b6f419df88d662bb7d18bd7c7e1","text":"Password and authentication code","correct":false},{"id":"f3499a9f28ab4d9412f8dc5e818c8ccd","text":"User name and password","correct":false},{"id":"59f2c8e6be7c2804d73e2f0bad9b26e8","text":"User name, password, and authentication code","correct":true},{"id":"36562a3012cb05bd90eed776b4760dc7","text":"User name and authentication code","correct":false}]},{"id":"d5512a42-0f94-11ea-8d71-362b9e155667","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following AWS services enable you to continuously monitor and record configuration changes of your resources?","explanation":"It can be easy to confuse Config and CloudTrail, since both are AWS management-and-governance tools. However, they operate differently. While CloudTrail provides event history of your AWS account activity, Config specifically focuses on listing the resources in your AWS account and presenting their configuration change history.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/config/","title":"AWS Config"}],"answers":[{"id":"2d80a80d60fea86242f99512dbac7529","text":"AWS Config","correct":true},{"id":"26ca9b29af36f84c577a85a80a58a381","text":"AWS CloudTrail","correct":false},{"id":"05f43441d2d29ae2bb38fc8596ca6ff7","text":"AWS Trusted Advisor","correct":false},{"id":"621f4719cc9f27432c4c095f76df474e","text":"Amazon GuardDuty","correct":false}]},{"id":"ff57921e-2faa-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following statements are true of the AWS Free Tier?","explanation":"All statements listed here are correct except for one. If you don’t use all your Free Tier benefits within the month, they don’t roll over to the next month.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/awsaccountbilling/latest/aboutv2/billing-free-tier.html","title":"Using the AWS Free Tier"}],"answers":[{"id":"e0a5844f80154f67479f312499e75d1a","text":"Usage must be kept below the Free Tier limits to avoid charges.","correct":true},{"id":"8723f65debe98902ae71daeac7ca33e0","text":"Upon creation of an AWS account, the user is automatically signed up for the Free Tier for 12 months.","correct":true},{"id":"fca0d4d0e7ba8ff0a86efa806423c98d","text":"AWS starts charging the regular rates for usage of services and resources when the Free Tier expires.","correct":true},{"id":"aec630c6387bfee54b18d0ca80ea994c","text":"Unused benefits that the Free Tier provides in a given month roll over to the next month.","correct":false}]},{"id":"41fd3ae6-76b4-4f5f-8ee6-4f5688f969dc","domain":"tech","question":"You want to use an AWS service that enables you to notify select Tech Support members in your company (via email) of any cloud-related issues to attend to. Which of the following services will accomplish that?","explanation":"With Simple Notification Service, or Amazon SNS, you can create and appropriately name a topic to which you publish your messages. Then the select Tech Support members can be subscribed to that topic to receive these messages as email notifications.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/sns/","title":"Amazon SNS"}],"answers":[{"id":"7ba6eb634dd2e14688216874c0948a82","text":"Simple Notification Service","correct":true},{"id":"e99b5e1a7bf908cbe637b87720eb88c2","text":"Simple Email Service","correct":false},{"id":"1f4072738a4917bea022b11256fb46a4","text":"Simple Workflow Service","correct":false},{"id":"142db9d2b615fcb75a6dd2e4a2a9eb2a","text":"Simple Queue Service","correct":false}]},{"id":"82395a22-1850-11ea-8d71-362b9e155667","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following are benefits of Amazon RDS read replicas?","explanation":"Amazon read replicas are copies of your source database instance and enhance performance by reducing the instance’s workload and increase availability when the instance fails. In addition, read replicas are designed for security because RDS sets up communication between them and the source DB instance using public key encryption. Automated backups are a feature of multi-AZ deployments, not a benefit of read replicas.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/rds/details/read-replicas/","title":"Amazon RDS Read Replicas"}],"answers":[{"id":"04698c3c0a8125713f9aa8b52980533f","text":"Automated backups","correct":false},{"id":"9a444c669290fc78c2a35ebd7978f501","text":"Enhanced performance","correct":true},{"id":"ef9fb3f2791771e8bae6858776183460","text":"Increased availability","correct":true},{"id":"acb398041387588e9008c86fa3065023","text":"Designed for security","correct":true}]},{"id":"d05a0228-8d82-4cef-8dfb-4e2cb3856a9f","domain":"security","question":"According to the Shared Responsibility Model, which of the following is AWS responsible for?","explanation":"Protecting the infrastructure that runs all of the services in the AWS Cloud is the responsibility of AWS. Such services include EC2 infrastructure - the hardware compute platform for running EC2 instances and Amazon Virtual Private Cloud, or VPC, which enables customers to provision a logically isolated section of the AWS Cloud to launch their resources. The subnets, security groups, and network access control lists configured in the VPC are the responsibility of the customer.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"Shared Responsibility Model"},{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/vpc/","title":"Amazon Virtual Private Cloud"}],"answers":[{"id":"fe11e14b29ee1462bdb7764b3ba2f4bd","text":"Security Groups","correct":false},{"id":"74cd215a46d2bd96fc35dad7ef313283","text":"Subnets","correct":false},{"id":"06ea336ee4a57004a721e76f5cdd9083","text":"Network Access Control Lists","correct":false},{"id":"28aaf85b7ba1e63aa22c1c645a4c22e4","text":"Elastic Cloud Compute (EC2) infrastructure","correct":true},{"id":"c33dcb724e4d74e54dbc8347d4402690","text":"Amazon Virtual Private Cloud","correct":true}]},{"id":"bcecb806-dc3d-42d5-abaf-92b78f78bf00","domain":"security","question":"Which of the below are TRUE statements when it comes to network security for an EC2 instance in AWS?","explanation":"Under the Shared Responsibility Model, AWS takes responsibility for managing all the hardware (including access, patching and other maintenance) and software required to deliver the service. In this scenario, AWS is responsible for the underlying network hardware, not the customer. However the customer is responsible for ensuring that only wanted, valid traffic reaches their EC2 instance through the use of Security Groups, Access Control Lists or Software Firewalls","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"The AWS Shared Responsibility Model"}],"answers":[{"id":"01407b8624848ffc3a63fcbb919421fb","text":"AWS is responsible for ensuring malicious traffic does not impair the network hardware","correct":true},{"id":"3bab15fdca03e0fc9fcb17e344d1ffed","text":"The customer is responsible for ensuring malicious traffic does not impair the network hardware","correct":false},{"id":"1dbd0eb41e4e90508191eb1f5a99b615","text":"The customer is responsible for ensuring unwanted traffic does not reach the EC2 instance","correct":true},{"id":"d06119c27ec0a4e3b321bd66da22fea2","text":"AWS is responsible for ensuring malicious traffic does not reach the EC2 instance","correct":false},{"id":"e61949c2c6f3b07d6b052aeed05cafd5","text":"AWS is responsible for ensuring unwanted traffic does not reach the EC2 instance","correct":false},{"id":"4aa6ca9653c0c4e24ff62399d1e4ca09","text":"The customer is responsible for ensuring malicious traffic does not reach the EC2 instance","correct":true}]},{"id":"86ed7d54-4495-435b-908a-b439c255c35d","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the five best practices does AWS Trusted Advisor use to eliminate unused, underutilized, and idle resources in your environment?","explanation":"AWS Trusted Advisor ensures cost optimization of your AWS account by eliminating unused, underutilized, and idle resources, which include EC2 instances, load balancers, EBS volumes, and elastic IP addresses.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/premiumsupport/technology/trusted-advisor/best-practice-checklist/","title":"AWS Trusted Advisor Best Practice Checks"}],"answers":[{"id":"07d2fdfae089a6e085811b22437de261","text":"Service limits","correct":false},{"id":"a39ae09f8be4327fc176cfeb76a0e366","text":"Cost optimization","correct":true},{"id":"45a75e44a713fdf94dbf1dbaa0749188","text":"Fault tolerance","correct":false},{"id":"2fae32629d4ef4fc6341f1751b405e45","text":"Security","correct":false},{"id":"9446a98ad14416153cc4d45ab8b531bf","text":"Performance","correct":false}]},{"id":"0eeaa82c-20b2-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following provides the least expensive Amazon S3 storage?","explanation":"Both Glacier and Glacier Deep Archive are for data archiving; as a result, they cost a lot less than the One Zone-Infrequent Access and Intelligent Tiering S3 storage classes, which are for more frequently accessed data. Glacier Deep Archive is the lowest cost option.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/s3/storage-classes/","title":"Amazon S3 Storage Classes"}],"answers":[{"id":"13c28d56109c12a096b5e325b65a1c01","text":"Intelligent Tiering","correct":false},{"id":"e2b0c2a0a664cef2184b3d17808db4ce","text":"One Zone-Infrequent Access","correct":false},{"id":"d2f79b4db321be04fd1439394fb99d3c","text":"Glacier Deep Archive","correct":true},{"id":"4def2a084469f97f6372bfaf0823941b","text":"Glacier","correct":false}]},{"id":"d65c52f9-7f9b-4765-b0a6-cf58294f7034","domain":"tech","question":"Which of the following statements is false regarding Amazon ElastiCache?","explanation":"All statements are correct about ElastiCache save for one. ElasticCache is designed to streamline read operations. Write operations cannot be performed with Elasticache","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonElastiCache/latest/APIReference/Welcome.html","title":"Amazon ElastiCache"},{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonElastiCache/latest/red-ug/WhatIs.html","title":"What is Amazon ElastiCache for Redis?"},{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonElastiCache/latest/mem-ug/WhatIs.html","title":"What is Amazon ElastiCache for Memcached?"}],"answers":[{"id":"0cb5de3d769c0ce3b66cea646faab2ea","text":"It saves common queries to enable faster retrieval of information than disk-based databases.","correct":false},{"id":"77f82ce3947b78092c1bc9c5bd5cc7f0","text":"It is used for making write operations to databases significantly faster three open-source in-memory caching engines.","correct":true},{"id":"bad6e5cdf0a4beb80181a0a2cf2f5793","text":"It reduces the administrative burden that comes with launching and managing a distributed cache.","correct":false},{"id":"b16ed17379f1b31504154714e5bb941a","text":"It makes it easier to set up, operate, and scale a distributed cache in the cloud.","correct":false}]},{"id":"alwhmkiv-aa40-zbsb-1app-zkbeiem7zvs3","domain":"concepts","question":"Under the Shared Responsibility Model, for which of the following does AWS not assume responsibility?","explanation":"Customers are responsible for their own customer data in the cloud. AWS manages the Networking, Hypervisor Configuration, and Physical Security","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"AWS shared Responsibility"}],"answers":[{"id":"6016c2bb7bd8dd79293094d37ebfea3f","text":"Customer data","correct":true},{"id":"5dd5aedeaa5de8a95f383a8e014b1e5d","text":"Physical security of AWS facilities","correct":false},{"id":"a5fa5746370b608090b994a97b49e98b","text":"Networking","correct":false},{"id":"1b837a3c0786d704da0c00c61b4d57b5","text":"Hypervisors","correct":false}]},{"id":"3a04d665-f391-4b59-93bc-8e7e60565b99","domain":"tech","question":"Your project manager (PM) tasked you with launching an instance for a web application to be developed for an NGO. The PM is especially interested in using an AWS service that provides predicable monthly pricing, and he expects the instance to have the ability to burst above the baseline level of CPU performance when needed. What AWS service should you use to launch this instance?","explanation":"Although EC2 could have been the correct answer, two things are key here: Predicable monthly pricing and instance ability to burst above the baseline level of CPU performance when needed. Lightsail accomplishes that; EC2 is more suitable for consistently high CPU performance, and costs vary according to usage.","links":[{"url":"https://lightsail.aws.amazon.com/ls/docs/en_us/articles/amazon-lightsail-frequently-asked-questions-faq","title":"Frequently Asked Questions in Amazon Lightsail"}],"answers":[{"id":"1dd30e8d60c2a200781dbcc9286f0919","text":"Elasticsearch Service","correct":false},{"id":"b21eea42e76007ac061cf37a5a41037d","text":"Lightsail","correct":true},{"id":"81b22456f78954c460ce2f531b5e048f","text":"EC2","correct":false},{"id":"bef6cb89241de238f082cb243307ad1b","text":"CloudFront","correct":false}]},{"id":"1db22272-d476-4034-844a-5d8d9fd40091","domain":"concepts","question":"A telecommunications company has his hired you as a consultant to develop a business case for moving its IT applications and infrastructure to AWS. The company’s leadership understands the agility value of the cloud, but the finance group is not interested in shifting capital expense to operating expense due to the company’s tax structure. What will you include in the business case to attempt to satisfy everyone at the company?","explanation":"Many companies capitalize reserved instance purchases, especially those with 3-year terms. Waiting for current infrastructure to fully depreciate will cause the company to miss the other cloud benefits that are available. Moving the company to an operating expense model will prove too large a task, and will most likely result in a rejected business case. Elastic infrastructure is definitely a benefit, but doesn't address the capitalization issue.","links":[{"url":"https://d1.awsstatic.com/whitepapers/aws_pricing_overview.pdf","title":"How AWS Pricing Works"}],"answers":[{"id":"b55403f80a04df0f30d6552d35188c46","text":"Suggest that the company wait to migrate to AWS until the current infrastructure is fully depreciated","correct":false},{"id":"8419aa56459afcd14644026053cc0cfc","text":"Show the company the TCO value of moving to an operating expense model","correct":false},{"id":"875be7dcedf2167b7fa3192f4c94b2a3","text":"Suggest that the company make reserved instance purchases and capitalize them","correct":true},{"id":"cd56c0654f075d81e563f7f6740b2cb8","text":"Show the value of an elastic infrastructure for avoiding wasted capacity","correct":false}]},{"id":"e3b24121-862f-4b1e-8f4e-18e6f3f9e1e8","domain":"concepts","question":"VMware Cloud on AWS allows companies to migrate and extend their on-premises VMware vSphere-based environments to AWS Cloud using Amazon EC2. Which of the following choices accurately classifies this deployment model?","explanation":"Hybrid deployments connect infrastructure and applications between cloud-based resources and existing resources that are not located in the cloud. VMware Cloud on AWS is an example of a hybrid deployment, since it involves the on-premises environments of VMware and the cloud-based services of AWS.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/hybrid/","title":"Hybrid Cloud with AWS"}],"answers":[{"id":"0fca8d17afc46bb08bd2d70a26cdf886","text":"On-Premises","correct":false},{"id":"c8e2277ecfb1427838c488c217f99466","text":"Cloud","correct":false},{"id":"d6eb128e4c8971dc397f021585391999","text":"Shared Services","correct":false},{"id":"fb1b6e23a3767d2a31ef7899e6dd3f1e","text":"Hybrid","correct":true}]},{"id":"0e20ce8c-1a57-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following statements is true of AWS Regions?","explanation":"AWS Regions are geographical areas that consist of locations called Availability Zones. Because they are isolated from each other, there is no automatic replication of resources between them. In addition, data transfer between Regions is not free; there is a charge associated with that.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/using-regions-availability-zones.html","title":"Regions, Availability Zones, and Local Zones"}],"answers":[{"id":"6f99c65ce03a0a9018c608fc49149883","text":"There are no charges for data transferred between them.","correct":false},{"id":"f941bbe63c60384543e03468d67e8a94","text":"They are independent geographical areas.","correct":true},{"id":"96676b55f4ae2e27083b81e373c80e5a","text":"They automatically replicate resources among each other.","correct":false},{"id":"3a4116551c9039850c094ec59ecc726c","text":"They are composed of Availability Zones.","correct":true}]},{"id":"f073f45a-0541-43a5-a1ae-4c67afb87086","domain":"security","question":"As an AWS customer, what is the best thing to do if you want to get periodic official statements to be notified of security and privacy events with AWS services?","explanation":"You will not get official security statements from the AWS News Blog, which provides current events regarding AWS. And while you can always send an email to request security announcements, chances are you will be redirected to the Security Bulletins page, where you can subscribe to an RSS feed to be updated on security and privacy issues.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/security/security-bulletins/?card-body.sort-by=item.additionalFields.bulletinDateSort&card-body.sort-order=desc","title":"Security Bulletins"}],"answers":[{"id":"ddd4a6bf26b1483b9221e364d190454f","text":"Email AWS directly to express your interest in receiving security announcements.","correct":false},{"id":"ab09f1b93a71ea2e9b2634438d8c954a","text":"Email AWS Security to express your interest in receiving security announcements.","correct":false},{"id":"335ec04e733ed7b0bacd46bf6948b866","text":"Subscribe to the AWS Security Bulletin RSS feed.","correct":true},{"id":"520267b96af385f180fa3fd9ec26dc51","text":"Subscribe to the AWS News Blog.","correct":false}]},{"id":"8r7r7n13-hvyw-63f9-gltg-21wwwmux0grq","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following best describes a system that will remain operational even in the event of a component failure?","explanation":"a fault-tolerant system will remain operational even in the event of a component failure.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/whitepapers/designing-fault-tolerant-applications/","title":"Building Fault-Tolerant Applications in the AWS Cloud"}],"answers":[{"id":"28cb2468ce3a85b4d10668ec48f5e4d6","text":"Scalable","correct":false},{"id":"9818cb0bfa2dfb200a8c078b1fe1c2fd","text":"Highly Available","correct":false},{"id":"a078ed5ade8df4aac54efbdb57e63ad2","text":"Elastic","correct":false},{"id":"7bf4251c070de07f503b12b9d341daea","text":"Fault-tolerant","correct":true}]},{"id":"a1237c57-f005-8048-710c-489f984ca8d0","domain":"tech","question":"Where would you find the AWS Attestation of Compliance Documentation for PCI DSS?","explanation":"AWS Artifact is your go-to, central resource for compliance-related information that matters to you. It provides on-demand access to AWS’ security and compliance reports and select online agreements. AWS Support's site provides general information about compliance, but does not hold the secure reports or certificates. AWS IAM is used to control security within your AWS Account. Amazon Macie is a data security classification service.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/artifact/","title":"AWS Artifact"}],"answers":[{"id":"26e8220e8fac28d2a1a9a18ca81aabd7","text":"AWS Support","correct":false},{"id":"1f7efb5a61d1162575c83917dd086ad7","text":"Amazon Macie","correct":false},{"id":"73bf7f67bbb8ede06c6d98f4133f9743","text":"AWS Identity and Access Management","correct":false},{"id":"60b018772cea138af5a8c452ed694734","text":"AWS Artifact","correct":true}]},{"id":"a0b65082-209c-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"tech","question":"By default, how many buckets per AWS Account can you create with the Amazon S3 service?","explanation":"By default, you can create up to 100 S3 buckets per AWS account. However, you can request for additional buckets by submitting a service limit increase.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AmazonS3/latest/dev/BucketRestrictions.html","title":"Bucket Restrictions and Limitations"}],"answers":[{"id":"f899139df5e1059396431415e770c6dd","text":"100","correct":true},{"id":"8e296a067a37563370ded05f5a3bf3ec","text":"25","correct":false},{"id":"cee631121c2ec9232f3a2f028ad5c89b","text":"500","correct":false},{"id":"d3d9446802a44259755d38e6d163e820","text":"10","correct":false}]},{"id":"smnrxkfv-dk56-snvh-i93e-or0vfomvccbz","domain":"concepts","question":"Which of the following are characteristics of cloud computing?","explanation":"The on-demand delivery via the internet of services with pay-as-you-go pricing characterizes cloud computing. Services incurred from a cloud services provider are operating expenses, not capital expenses. Capital Expenditure (CAPEX) is less common with the cloud, in favour of Operational Expenditure (OPEX). Skills and training for personnel are required to leverage Cloud Computing","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/what-is-cloud-computing/","title":"What is Cloud Computing?"}],"answers":[{"id":"ebc744edbd870e96fe9e680b407ad053","text":"On-demand delivery","correct":true},{"id":"2b34d3fef0b313e0047a2557d9842378","text":"Pay-as-you-go pricing","correct":true},{"id":"481f1c72f1007c1ac8e4a484b47af4f2","text":"Cloud charges are Capital Expenditures.","correct":false},{"id":"dcfe379beaf88dbe9d59e7fcecf6f98a","text":"Services are delivered via the Internet.","correct":true},{"id":"9b670633c5238ca5a17dd651c3a63662","text":"No extra skills or training are required.","correct":false}]},{"id":"d29bb03a-1a55-11ea-978f-2e728ce88125","domain":"security","question":"According to the AWS Shared Responsibility Model, which of the following is the customer responsible for? (Choose 3)","explanation":"AWS is responsible for protecting the infrastructure that runs its services. Such services include Amazon VPC, which enables a customer to provision a logically isolated section of the AWS Cloud. This section is simply referred to as a virtual private cloud, or VPC. So, while AWS is responsible for the software (Amazon VPC), the customer is responsible for the virtual network created with that software (VPC), as well as whatever goes in it. This includes subnets (each of which consist of a range of IP addresses) and security groups (each of which acts as a virtual firewall to control inbound and outbound traffic).","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/compliance/shared-responsibility-model/","title":"Shared Responsibility Model"},{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/vpc/latest/userguide/what-is-amazon-vpc.html","title":"What Is Amazon VPC?"}],"answers":[{"id":"452be8d0a4b871d9b4ec8f7e323a17a2","text":"Virtual Private Clouds (VPCs)","correct":true},{"id":"1d7c6a62b7a045346e19186c911b38a1","text":"Amazon VPC Service","correct":false},{"id":"74cd215a46d2bd96fc35dad7ef313283","text":"Subnets","correct":true},{"id":"9175bb34d0aede26315b313b9432bcbb","text":"Security groups","correct":true}]},{"id":"ef918c09-219a-45b3-b1cc-f5b02cdbfc1d","domain":"concepts","question":"What type of placement group should you use to spread Amazon EC2 instances across logical partitions so that they don’t share the same underlying hardware?","explanation":"With a partition placement group, EC2 instances are placed into logical segments called partitions, each of which has its own set of racks to supply its network and power source. This level of isolation is designed to prevent the impact of hardware failure within your application.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/AWSEC2/latest/UserGuide/placement-groups.html","title":"Placement Groups"}],"answers":[{"id":"66f9c6c5b672ee16deeef6e4503cb4bc","text":"Reserve","correct":false},{"id":"180bc3b1c5619aaef40e803f49921012","text":"Spread","correct":false},{"id":"249694a485fc5d3289c38986b4f8e887","text":"Cluster","correct":false},{"id":"3349300356cb3141ea939dcbdf749789","text":"Partition","correct":true}]},{"id":"918c058b-8c3d-4858-aa1b-de986b3379af","domain":"security","question":"Which following statement is true of newly created security groups with their default rules?","explanation":"By default, new security groups start with only an outbound rule to allow all traffic to leave the instances. You must add rules to enable any inbound traffic.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/vpc/latest/userguide/VPC_SecurityGroups.html","title":"Security Groups for Your VPC"}],"answers":[{"id":"8fbe4c39dc7d852a0b8aaa5b889b1ff1","text":"New security groups block outbound traffic and allow all incoming traffic.","correct":false},{"id":"d00cd55aa36c87aedb13b4c0829aa462","text":"New security groups block both incoming and outbound traffic.","correct":false},{"id":"66152806bd7636ccc1a33303917cdddd","text":"New security groups allow only outbound traffic and block all incoming traffic.","correct":true},{"id":"d21ab4dffc222de4dfe6fddddca20b1f","text":"New security groups allow both incoming and outbound traffic.","correct":false}]},{"id":"82a1ac91-eb42-41c9-b216-39000de68a5c","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following statements are true about who can use IAM roles?","explanation":"A role can be used by either an IAM user in the same AWS account as the role or a user in a different AWS account. A role can also be used by a web service that AWS offers; a prime example is Amazon EC2.","links":[{"url":"https://docs.aws.amazon.com/IAM/latest/UserGuide/id_roles_terms-and-concepts.html","title":"IAM Role Terms and Concepts"}],"answers":[{"id":"31124384faad90d323f0ac8b670e3d5f","text":"An IAM user in the same AWS account as the role","correct":true},{"id":"85f661e32207f8f663f531db040bc97a","text":"A web service offered by AWS","correct":true},{"id":"bf2d86ed19745c25bb11a0239b17b7a5","text":"An IAM user in a different AWS account than the role","correct":true},{"id":"df8acd03a312147855a4dbb0fc3cad51","text":"A web service offered by providers other than AWS","correct":false}]},{"id":"55632ec1-3922-4d04-80c0-ff9b5b21c2d2","domain":"billing","question":"Which of the following are AWS EC2 reserved pricing types?","explanation":"Reserved instances have three main pricing models, Standard, Convertible and Scheduled. Each model is targeted with a specific use case and benefits from its own level of discounted price","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/ec2/pricing/","title":"Amazon EC2 pricing"}],"answers":[{"id":"e507a844b940fd588a1cbb5bb46fd4fe","text":"Standard Reserved Instances","correct":true},{"id":"c9e63a71aa24afcde5e964d2530e2524","text":"Compute Reserved Instances","correct":false},{"id":"bd1ad3385adf098b2e87d2bb75d87e39","text":"Scalable Reserved Instances","correct":false},{"id":"fe501a6493589e0d87e90fd0b4361e6f","text":"Convertable Reserved Instances","correct":true},{"id":"c81edad1f6d23ac52025cde1cf22ba7b","text":"Scheduled Reserved Instances","correct":true}]},{"id":"e9yzvx4u-z9ss-opgg-lwg4-h390rywj4hat","domain":"security","question":"Which of the following AWS services controls Authentication and Authorization within an AWS account?","explanation":"IAM (Identity and Access Management) controls Authentication and Authorization within an AWS account. Security Groups and Access Control Lists are tools within IAM that can help make that control easier to manage. AWS Shield is a separate service that helps protect resources from external attacks.","links":[{"url":"https://aws.amazon.com/iam/details/","title":"About IAM"}],"answers":[{"id":"41dff7155cc7aeb11c06434f6a450bb3","text":"IAM","correct":true},{"id":"637d82e8a7206e87344161109cf7112d","text":"AWS Shield","correct":false},{"id":"303a25c2935ec1fdb01208b6f4f65688","text":"Access Control Lists","correct":false},{"id":"fe11e14b29ee1462bdb7764b3ba2f4bd","text":"Security Groups","correct":false}]}]}}}}
